Viewers all over the world, whatever medium you are using to watch us right now,
I command that affliction in your life to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Pain in your blood, pain in your kidneys, wherever it is located - leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be captured, in the name of Jesus!
For the glory of God - be captured, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever that disease is located - leave my people!
Leave my people!
Right now, begin to confess your freedom. Confess your healing.
I am healed!
My kidney is healed!
My liver is healed!
My blood is healed!
My tendon is healed!
My bone is healed!
Confess your freedom, healing!
Viewers all over the world, begin to confess your healing, in the name of Jesus!
In the blood of Jesus!
Jesus says you are healed!
You are healed!
Every sickness, disease, wherever it is located - be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
That one with pain, hear pain no more!
Hear the voice of affliction no more!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, open your lips and begin to send it back to the pit of hell!
It comes from the pit of hell. Send it back to the pit of hell!
Confess your healing right now.
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 02/09/2018